DSA Data structure is a popular course teached to students for enhancing their effieciency while writing the code.
RAM Random Access Memory (RAM) is the hardware component used to store data that is actively being used by a processor.
CPU CPU stands for the Central Processing Unit. It is the processing chip that serves as the "brains" of a device .
ROM stands for Read-Only Memory. This is memory that can only be read from and is not electronically modifiable after being manufactured.
Algorithm  At a basic level, algorithms are simply specific procedures used to solve computational problems.
IDE An integrated development environment is a software tool where developers can write code and run their programs. 
BVB College belong to Kle tech university located in vidyanagar hubballi. This project is builded by students of this college .
